runitonce.com 2019-12-03

# Data Protection Policy | Run It Once

### Privacy Policy

We respect your privacy and the use and protection of your Personal Information. RIO may request and/or collect information from you on a voluntary basis when you: Register with us, Post on our site (including forum, message board, or chat) or when you send questions or comments via email to RIO’s customer support. The requested information may include personal information such as your name and e-mail address. 

Run It Once provides the services and content at [www.runitonce.com](https://www.runitonce.com/) as a discretionary service that an individual is free to use or not and is free to purchase or not. 

As part of our regular business conduct, we may share information with companies or individuals providing services or acting on our behalf, such as companies providing technological or fulfillment services. In the event that there is a change of corporate ownership, the new owners will of course be provided with our files, including information you have submitted. We will also share information with government officials, including law enforcement officials or court authorities, in order to cooperate with a legitimate investigation.  
Unless we tell you first (such as at the time we collect information from you), or unless it is part of a specific program or feature in which you have elected to participate, we do not share personally identifiable information that we have collected (such as name or e-mail address) with other, third-party companies for their own commercial or marketing purposes.  
From time to time we may include at the Site links to other websites as a service to you. The third party sites are operated by companies that are outside of our control, and your activities at those sites will be governed by the policies and practices of those third parties. We encourage you to review the privacy practices of these third parties before disclosing any personally identifiable information, as we are not responsible for the privacy practices of those sites 

### EU-US Privacy Shield For Non-U.S. Users

Please note that we may collect, store and process your personal information in the United States or in other countries outside of the country where you live. The United States and/or these countries may not offer the same level of privacy protection for your personal information as is offered in the country in which you live. To address privacy concerns, we comply with the EU-US Privacy Shield Framework as set forth by the US Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information from European Union member countries. We hereby certify that we adhere to the Privacy Shield Principles of Notice, Choice, Accountability for Onward Transfer, Security, Data Integrity and Purpose Limitation, Access, and Recourse, Enforcement and Liability. If there is any conflict between the policies in this Privacy Policy and the Privacy Shield Principles, the Privacy Shield Principles shall govern. To learn more about the Privacy Shield program, and to view our certification page, please visit https://www.privacyshield.gov/. We will use our reasonable best efforts to maintain the security of your personal information, provide opt-in/opt-out notices where personal information is collected as required, use data in a manner consistent with its original purpose for collection, and offer mechanisms for you to assist in ensuring your personal information is accurate and reliable. In the event that we transfer your personal information or any other data regulated by Privacy Shield to a third party, we could be liable for any damages resulting from violations of applicable law arising from such onward transfer, provided that we were responsible for the event giving rise to such damage. 

You have the right to access, correct, or delete your personal information, and you may also limit our use or disclosure of your personal information, provided that you send us notice of any such request in an email to [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#e0939590908f9294a092958e89948f8e8385ce838f8d) or by mail to:

Compliance Officer  
Run It Once Inc.  
1919 S Jones Blvd, Ste G,  
Las Vegas, NV,  
89146 

In compliance with the EU-US Privacy Shield Principles, we commit to resolve complaints about your privacy and our collection or use of your personal information. European Union citizens with inquiries or complaints regarding this Privacy Policy should first contact us via email at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#51222421213e23251123243f38253e3f32347f323e3c), or by writing a letter to us at:

Compliance Officer  
Run It Once Inc.  
1919 S Jones Blvd, Ste G,  
Las Vegas, NV,  
89146 

We have further committed to refer unresolved privacy complaints under the US-EU Privacy Shield Principles to an independent dispute resolution mechanism, JAMS ADR, an alternative dispute resolution provider located in the United States. If you do not receive timely acknowledgment of your complaint, or if your complaint is not satisfactorily addressed, please visit the JAMS ADR website at <https://www.jamsadr.com/eu-us-privacy-shield> for more information and to file a complaint. The enforcement authority having jurisdiction over Run It Once’s compliance with EU Privacy Shield is the U.S. Federal Trade Commission. In certain limited conditions, individuals may invoke binding arbitration before the Privacy Shield Panel to be created by the U.S. Department of Commerce and the European Commission. We may be required, and therefore reserve the right, to share your personal information in response to lawful information requests from governmental authorities or as otherwise required by law, including to meet national security or law enforcement requirements. In instances where we disclose personal information to a third party, or if that information is to be used for a purpose different than the purpose for which it was originally collected, you may opt-out of such onward transfer of your personal information by notifying us of your decision by emailing us at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#6f1c1a1f1f001d1b2f1d1a01061b00010c0a410c0002) or by writing a letter to us at:

Compliance Officer  
Run It Once Inc.  
1919 S Jones Blvd, Ste G,  
Las Vegas, NV,  
89146 

An opt-in choice will also be provided for sensitive personal information. 

By accessing the website, you are transferring your personal information to the United States and you consent to that transfer. If you are accessing the website from Asia or any other region with laws or regulations governing personal data collection, use, and disclosure, that differ from United States laws, and the country is not a party to US-EU Privacy Shield, the disclosure of personal information pursuant to this Privacy Policy is at your own risk. Except as expressly stated in this Privacy Policy, we make no representation that the practices described in this Privacy Policy are compliant with the laws where you live that apply to the collection, security, use, and disclosure of personal information.
